coachfactory.com 2015-02-15

# Security & Privacy

Coach, Inc. (the "Company") and our brands value your trust. We collect certain information when you visit our U.S. site www.coach.com (the “Site”), in order to improve your shopping experience and allow us to better communicate with you regarding our products and services. This privacy policy is intended to assist you in understanding what information we gather when you visit the Site, how we use that information, and the safeguards we have in place to protect the information. This privacy policy only applies to information we collect at www.coach.com.

By using and submitting information to our Site, you are agreeing that we may collect, use and disclose the information we collect in accordance with the purposes and uses identified in this policy. For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of the Site, please review our Legal Statement.

### Information We Collect Online

#### Personal Information

For purposes of this privacy policy, "personal information" means any information by which someone can be personally identified, including name, address, telephone number, email address, billing and account information, credit or debit card information, and other information incidental to providing goods or services. We collect personal information from you only when you voluntarily provide us with this information, such as when placing an order through the Site or registering your Coach product on the Site; establishing an account or adding information to your account such as by setting up a wish list, gift reminders, or address book entries; entering a contest; taking a survey; contacting us with a comment or question; requesting a catalog; signing up to receive emails about our latest products and services; requesting to receive investor alerts; or applying for a job online. While not personal information by itself, the Company also collects and retains information about purchases you make on the Site.

#### Browsing Information; Cookies

When you visit the Site, our web servers may automatically recognize certain non-personally identifiable information about you, such as your domain name, access provider, IP address, and browser language. The Site also uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. The information collected from cookies allows us to provide better customer service to you and improve features of our Site in a variety of ways, including by determining whether you have visited the Site in the past and which pages of our Site you have visited. We also may use cookies and/or a technology known as clear gifs to help us confirm your receipt of and response to our emails and to provide you a more personalized experience. Please note that certain pages of the Site may not function properly if cookies are turned off. Please consult your web browser’s Help documentation for more information about how to turn cookies on and off your browser.

We may use third party advertising companies to serve Company advertisements on our Site or other sites you may visit. To accomplish this, these companies may employ anonymous cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness and understand your visits to our Site and other web sites. These selected companies also provide this information to us which we use for marketing purposes. If you would like more information about this practice click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). The Company also has chosen a company, Omniture, to assist us in understanding your use of the Site. Omniture may place cookies on your computer to receive information about your browsing and buying activity on the Site, and help us to provide you with a more personalized shopping experience. If you would like to opt out of these particular services, please click [here](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/policy).

### How We Use Your Information

We use personal information collected on the Site for the following purposes:

  * for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered (for example, to purchase a product, process a return or provide you with a gift reminder); 
  * to improve the content, appearance and utility of the Site; 
  * to understand your needs and preferences; 
  * to develop, market, sell or provide products and services; 
  * to conduct surveys, research and evaluations; 
  * to manage and develop our business and operations, administer accounts, and collect and process payments; 
  * to detect and protect us and other third parties against negligence, fraud, theft and other illegal activities; 
  * as permitted by, and to comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements, process or provisions; 
  * if you submit a resume online, we may use the information you provide solely for the purpose of evaluating you as a candidate for employment and to contact you about prospective employment. 

In order to serve you better, we may combine information you provide to us on the Site with information you provide to us in other ways, such as in our retail stores, and with information from third parties including demographic or public information.

### How We May Share Information

We may share your information collected on this Site with its subsidiaries or affiliated companies, including those located in other countries.

We also may share your information with selected third parties who provide services to us, including to process payments, provide electronic online investor information, monitor Site activity, serve Site content, help to maintain our customer database, administer emails, surveys, or contests and administer and maintain employment application information. Such third parties may have access to, store and process your personal information to provide services on our behalf, which may occur in the United States or in countries outside of the United States. Our service providers are not authorized to use your information for any purpose other than to provide the contracted services.

We also must always reserve the right to disclose information about you as required by law, in response to legal process including law enforcement requests, and where needed to protect the safety, property, or legal rights of users of the Site, or the Company or its affiliates or third parties.

Occasionally we may provide a link to a third party website, for example to conduct a survey for the Company. If you elect to provide your personal information on that third party website, this information will be subject to that third party website's privacy policy and security practices. We are not responsible or liable for any content presented by or contained on any independent website, including, but not limited to, any advertising claims or marketing practices. We also are not responsible or liable for any privacy or security policies of these third party sites.

In the unlikely event that the Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired by another company, or due to any merger, reorganization or liquidation, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. Your personal information will remain subject to any pre-existing privacy policy unless you consent otherwise.

### Children’s Privacy

We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet and does not knowingly request or collect personally identifiable information online from any person under the age of thirteen.

### Security

We use certain security measures to protect the personal information you submit to the Site. For example, when you provide any order information, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, an encryption tool that provides security while transmitting this information over the Internet. We also use firewall technology, password controls, and other technological and procedural safeguards in maintaining the Site. Although we have implemented the above security measures for this Site, you should be aware that 100% security is not possible.

### Managing Your Personal Information

To allow us to serve you better we encourage you to regularly review and update your personal information.

You may obtain upon request a summary of the personal information on record with us. You also may request that we correct any such personal information about you, remove such information from its marketing databases, or dispose of any or all personal information about you.

To make any request described above, or if you have any questions about this privacy policy, send an email to [comments@coach.com](mailto:comments@coach.com) or contact:

Coach Consumer Service   
One Coach Way   
Jacksonville, Florida 32218   
1-800-444-3611 or 1-904-741-3090   
M-F 8 am – 11 pm EST   
Sat 9 am – 7 pm EST   
Sun 11 am – 7 pm EST

When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact email address, name, mailing address and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.

Following any of these requests, some of your personal information may be retained for a period of time; for example, to process a pending transaction you have made through the Site, to follow-up on a request, resolve a dispute, or for similar reasons. Some personal information also may continue to be stored on “back up” files for financial, legal or technical reasons.

If you do not wish to receive email from Coach in the future, you can unsubscribe by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any Coach email that you receive, emailing us at [comments@coach.com](mailto:comments@coach.com) with your request to be removed from our email list, by calling consumer services at (800) 444-3611 or by clicking [here](https://e.coach.com/servlet/website/ResponseForm?JhHJoE3LI1glNI_.40hkt).

### Updating This Policy; Notices

The Company reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this privacy policy at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will be considered your consent to those changes. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email.

### Effective Date

This policy is effective February 3, 2010.
